Guide to the Benjamin Newton Duke Papers, 1834-1969, bulk 1890-1929. RL.00328
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Alexander H. Sands, Jr., 1910-1918; 2.5 Linear Feet
  - Correspondence, 1914 May-1915 (Box 156)
  - Letterbook, 1910 August 19-1915 September 14 (Box 157)
  - Letterbook, 1915 September 23-1918 June 11 (Box 158)
  - Financial accounts: Southern Audit Co. of New York, Inc., 1914-1915 (Box 156)
  - Check registers, 1912-1913 (Box 156)
  - Check stubs, 1910 April-1914 June; 3 folders (Box 156)
  - Check stubs, 1914 November-1915 May; 1 Volumes (Box 159)
  - Check stubs: special account, 1915-1916; 2 Volumes (Box 159)
  - Check stubs: Reyhing & Co., 1914 (Box 160)
  - Daybook, 1914-1915 (Box 160)
  - Ledger, 1914-1915 (Box 160)
  - Receipts, 1913-1915; 4 folders (Box 160)